# Victor Feijó

## Contact

Shenzhen, China victor.feijoa@gmail.com +86 18923881356 github.com/victorfeijo

## Languages

Portuguese native English fluent Chinese beginner

## **Engineering Skills**

#### languages

- Ruby JavaScript
- Python NodeJS

#### databases

- MySQL Redis
  - PostgreSQL
- ElasticSearch

## frameworks

- Rails React Redux
- React-Native Django
- Express RSpec Jest

## devops

- Ansible Nginx
- Capistrano Docker

#### web infrastructure

- Amazon Heroku
- Google Cloud Plataform

## **PROFILE**

Passionate software engineer with 5+ years of coding experience. I also have a bachelor's degree in computer science at UFSC. Here's a list of keywords that better describe me: Proactivity, self-learning, leadership, creativity, flexibility, discipline, teamwork, and constant feedback.

## **EDUCATION**

**B.Sc.** in Computer Science

Federal University of Santa Catarina (UFSC)

**Extra English Course** 

Federal University of Santa Catarina (UFSC)

2014 - 2018

2014 - 2016

06/2019 - now

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Senior Software Engineer

ae.studio

Responsible for the development of different projects for big and small companies in the USA market. Working in a Full Stack position using many modern technologies such as Ruby on Rails, React/Redux, React Native, NodeJS, Typescript and Python.

#### **Consulting Software Engineer**

08/2018 - 06/2019

Incentiv.me

Full Stack engineer on a crowdfunding application for social projects. The application is developed in technologies such as Ruby on Rails, MihtirIJS, PostgREST, and PostgreSQL. In addition to working with software maintenance, architecture, and infrastructure management, I was also responsible for hiring and managing a team of 3 engineers.

## **Lead Software Engineer**

10/2018 - 05/2019

Zygo

Responsible for the company's new product development leading a team of 3 engineers and 1 UX Designer. In charge of making software architecture decisions that guarantee's application scalability and reliability.

#### **Software Engineer**

02/2016 - 09/2018

Zygo

Full Stack application development using Ruby on Rails, Python, Redis, React/Redux, and Bootstrap. I engaged in many projects from mobile development to data processing using Google Cloud machine learning API's. I also worked with infrastructure setup (Amazon AWS and Google Cloud) and technologies such as Serverless, Ansible, Nginx, and Capistrano.

#### **Software Developer**

03/2015 - 01/2016

Computer Security Laboratory (LabSEC) at UFSC

Research and development of computer security software. Use of technologies for digital signature validation, certification authorities, and PDF documents signing.

## **Scholarship**

09/2014 - 03/2015

PET UFSC

Responsible for helping other students, maintenance of Linux servers, and organization of technology conferences.

For more information, please see GitHub profile.